[ Background Conversations ]
[ 背景噪声 ]
&gt;&gt; Welcome.
&gt;&gt; 欢迎
This year, we are delighted to
在今年中我们很高兴引进了一个新的
introduce a new framework in iOS
iOS 11 操作系统的框架（framework）
11 called Core NFC, that would
叫做“Core NFC”
allow your apps to integrate NFC
它将允许你所开发的 app 与 iPhone 7 以及 iPhone 7 Plus上
on iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus.
的 NFC 芯片相兼容
Using Core NFC, apps can
通过使用 Core NFC 框架应用程序可以
interact with their physical
与物理
environment and the real-world
环境以及现实世界中
objects within it.
物体的互动
You may already know that Apple
你可能已经了解到
Pay uses NFC for complex
Apple Pay 会应用 NFC
payment.
处理复杂的交易行为
Now, with the introduction of
现在随着 Core NFC 框架的引入
Core NFC, you will be able to
你将可以
use NFC in your applications to
在你的应用程序中使用 NFC
create new and innovative user
开发出全新的 富有创造性的
experiences with the iPhone.
iPhone 用户体验
In this session, we will give
下面我们将给大家
you a brief overview of new
简要介绍一下
field communications, what is
近场通信
supported in the Core NFC
Core NFC 框架所支持的功能
framework, the requirements and
要求标准
details for using it, and some
使用细节以及
example code.
一些示范代码
To start off, let's talk a
首先让我们讨论一下
little bit about Near Field
近场
Communication.
通信
Near Field Communication, known
近场通信即 NFC
simply as NFC, is a wireless
是一种无线通信技术
technology that allows the
它可以让
exchange of information between
临近的设备
devices that are within close
进行
proximity.
数据交换
Limited to a range of just a few
距离限制在
centimeters.
几厘米内
NFC is actually a collection of
NFC 实际上是一些
a number of different standards
不同的传输标准
and protocols.
与传输协议的组合
All of these standards coexist
这些标准同时存在
and are used in different
并使用在不同的
applications.
app 中
You may have seen or had
你可能已经看到过
experience with NFC text.
或是感受过 NFC 文字传输功能
The small little stickers or
即使是很小的一张贴纸或者
cards which can be read
卡片
wirelessly by an NFC reader.
都可被 NFC 阅读器无线识别
NFC text comes in a wide variety
NFC 文档可与各种形状
of shapes, sizes, and
大小
capacities.
以及功能相
They are classified into five
它们被分为 5 个类型
categories, known as Type 1
从 Type 1
through Type 5.
到 Type 5
Each one corresponding to a
每种类型对应一个
different standard.
不同的标准
For example, Type 3 texts are
例如 Type 3
based on FEDECA [assumed
是基于 FeliCa 标准
spelling] and Type 4 is based on
Type 4 是
ISO-14443.
基于 ISO-14443
The NFC Forum has defined the
NFC Forum 制定了关于
NFC Data Exchange Format, or
NFC 数据交换格式
NDEF for short, as a common
简称 NDEF 做为一种通用的
messaging format for exchanging
信息交换格式
data in a standardized way among
它为不同的文字类别
the different text types.
进行标准化的数据传输
Now that we have covered some
现在我们了解了一些
NFC basics, let's take a look at
关于 NFC 的基础知识
what you can do with Core NFC.
让我们看一下用 Core NFC 能做什么
For the initial launch of Core
在 Core NFC 首发中
NFC, we have focused on NFC Tag
我们将重点放在 NFC 标签的读取上
Reading, which can be used to
这可以在很多方面
enhance the user experience in a
提升用户体验
Potential applications include
可能的 app 包括
connecting user to location or
将用户和地理位置
context-specific content,
或与环境相关的内容联系起来
connecting physical hardware
将实体硬件
with your application, and even
与你的 app 相连接
for in-store product information
甚至用于追踪店内商品信息
or inventory tracking.
或库存信息
In addition, NFC Tags can be
NFC Tags 还可以
used in place of QR codes.
代替二维码
Core NFC will allow your
Core NFC 可以让你的 app
application to read any NDEF
读取任何 NDEF
formatted tag.
格式的标签
This greatly simplifies the
这极大程度的简化了
process of reading tags within
应用程序读取标签的过程
your application or for having
也简化了应用程序要
to deal with the different
应对不同标准的麻烦
Tag reading is supported on
Phone 7 和 iPhone 7 Plus
iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus.
都支持标签读取
At this time, Core NFC does not
目前 Core NFC 不支持
support writing or formatting
输出或格式设置
There are two requirements for
在你的应用程序中使用 Core NFC
using Core NFC in your
有两个要求
First, Core NFC is an
首先 Core NFC 是一个
entitlement-protective
权限保护
framework.
框架
You will need to turn on the
你需要在 Xcode 中打开
Near Field Communication Tag
读取近场通信标签
Reading Capability from Xcode to
来获得
get this entitlement.
这一权限
However, this capability would
但是这个 Xcode 的功能将不会
[inaudible] released at WWDC.
做为种子（seed）计划在 WWDC 上公布
In the meantime, you can
但是通过访问 Apple Developer 网站的
manually request this
“Certificates, Identifiers andProfiles”
entitlement by visiting the
页面
Certificates, Identifiers and
你可以
Profiles page on the Apple
手动申请
Developer website.
这一权限
The second requirement for Core
Core NFC 的第二个要求
NFC is a Scan Usage Description.
是一个扫描使用的描述（Scan Usage Description）
This string is required in your
在你的应用属性列表文件（P-list）中
application's info P-list file,
需要用到这个字符串
and it will be displayed to the
在你的 app 开始进行 NFC 扫描的时候
user when your application
这个字符串会
starts NFC scanning.
显示给用户
For more information, you can
想要了解更多信息
watch the WWDC session, Privacy
可以观看 WWDC 有关“隐私与你的 App”
and Your Apps.
这一部分
Now that you have configured
现在你正确地设置了你的项目
your project correctly, let's
让我们来看
review some additional details
关于 Core NFC
about tag reading with the Core
读取标签的
NFC framework.
一些其他的细节
First, tag reading is an
首先标签读取是一个
on-demand process, meaning that
被动的处理过程意思是
your application has to initiate
你的 app 需要用一个对话
a tag reading activity using a
来主动发起标签
session.
读取这一行为
Second, your application has to
第二你的程序必须处在
be visible and foregrounded in
前台和可视状态中
order to start a tag reading
才能开始
activity.
读取这一行为
A tag reading session will be
如果你的 app 转为后台
ended if your application is
或是转为不可见时
backgrounded or ceases to be
也将被终止
Next, each tag reading activity
还有标签读取的行为
is limited to 60 seconds at a
被限制在每次
time.
60 秒钟
If a session has timed out or
如果会话过期或未经过验证
invalidated, your application
你的程序必须
must create a new session to
建立一个新的对话
initiate another tag reading
发起一个新的标签读取
activity.
行为
You can configure a session to
你可以设置对话
read either a single tag or
让它读取单个标签
multiple tags.
或是多个标签
In a single tag reading mode,
在读取单个标签的状态下
the session will be ended
标签读取完成之后
automatically after a tag is
对话会自动终止
On the other hand, a multi-tag
然而读取多个标签的对话
reading session will remain
将始终保持在活动状态
active until canceled by the
直到被用户终止
user, or the 60-second timeout
或是 60 秒后
is reached.
对话过期
Finally, as mentioned
最后像之前提到的那样
previously, the NFC Usage String
你的属性清单中定义的
defined in your info P-list will
“NFC 使用字符串”
be displayed to the user while
（NFC Usage String）
the tag reading activity is in
在标签读取的过程中
progress.
将会被显示给用户
We have provided a sample
我们在这个演讲中
application along with this
提供了一个应用程序的示例
presentation to demonstrate the
来示范怎样使用
use of Core NFC.
Core NFC
Consider the case where you want
比如说你想
to take a physical kind of
清点库存
Here, we are showing you the key
在这里我们展示了
user interaction sequence of the
用户与示例应用程序交互的
sample application.
一些关键步骤
The sample application consists
示例应用程序包括
of a main table view, and a Scan
一个主要的表格视图
button.
和一个扫描键
Every time an inventory item is
每次扫描一件库存商品的时候
scanned, it is displayed as a
表格中就出现新的一行
role entry in this main table
显示该记录
Just click on the Scan button to
只需点击扫描键
start a tag scanning.
来开始扫描标签
This UI will be presented to the
这一用户界面
user hopefully on top of your
在扫描过程开始后
application once tag scanning
最好是显示在
has begun.
你的程序视图的最前面
During tag scanning, the user's
在标签扫描的过程中
description string is displayed
描述的字串显示在
within the UI.
用户界面中
At any time, the user can hit
用户可以随时点击取消键
the Cancel button to stop a tag
终止标签扫描的过程
scanning, which will invalidate
这将会终止读取的
the reader session.
对话过程
The UI will get updated once an
当一个 NFC 标签被成功读取后
NFC tag has been successfully
用户界面会被更新
Here, we have configured our
在这里我们将读取对话
reader session to be single tag
设置为读取
read mode.
单个标签的模式
Finally, the overlaid UI will be
最后当读取标签的对话结束之后
dismissed, and the application
叠加在前面的用户界面会消失
will be foregrounded once the
应用程序会变回为
tag reading session has ended.
最前面的视图
All right.
好
Let's walk through the code
让我们一起看一下
together from the sample
这个示例
application we have just shown.
应用程序的代码
At a high level, you would need
总体来说在你的 app 中
to perform these three easy
你需要简单的 3 个步骤
steps to enable tag reading in
来实现标签的读取
your application.
首先使用
First, adopt the NFC NDEF Reader
NFCNDEFReaderSessionDelegate
Session Delegate Protocol.
协议
Next, create an instance of the
然后创建 NFCNDEFReaderSession 这一类的
NFC NDEF Reader Session Class,
一个对象
and provide it with your
并委托（delegate）
delegate.
首先使用
Finally, start a reader session
最后用 Begin 这一方法
using the Begin method, and
开始读取（reader）对话
handle the delegate callbacks.
并处理委托的回调
Here is a cool snippet from the
这里有实例应用中的一段代码
sample application, illustrating
来说明这三个步骤
To start off, we import the Core
首先我们在代码中
NFC framework into the code.
引用了 Core NFC 框架
Here we adopt the delegate
这里我们在表格视图控制器里
protocol in Table View
使用了委托
Controller, which will handle
它将会处理
the two required callbacks.
两个必要的回调
They invalidate with error and
它们处理错误
detect NDEF.
并识别 NDEF
The invalidate with error
错误回调
callback will notify your
在读取标签的活动停止的时候
application when a tag reading
将会通知你的 app
This can happen for a variety of
这可能由一系列的
reasons.
原因引起
For example, a tag has been
例如在读取单个标签的对话中
successfully read in a single
一个标签被
tag read session.
成功的读取了
The user has chosen to stop the
或是用户
tag scanning activity.
停止了扫描
The 3-second timeout has expired
或是 60 秒钟的时限超时了
or the application is no longer
或者是程序
in the foreground.
不在前台了
The specific session object
在第一个变量中指定的对话
will be invalidated after the
在程序退出之后
function exits.
就无效了
A new reader session instance is
要读取新的标签
required for additional tag
需要一个新的
reading.
reader 对话
The detect NDEFs will be invoked
每次 NDEF 从一个标签中被读取的时候
every time an NDEF has been read
检测 NDEF
from an NFC tag.
就会被激活
Your application can then grab
你的 app 就可以
the payload from the NDEF
从 NDEF 信息中获取其携带的数据
message, decode it, and handle
解码并适当的
the message as appropriate.
处理信息
Finally, we have an extra method
最后我们外加一个方法
that links to the Scan button
给扫描按钮
for starting a single tag read
让它开始一个读取
session.
单个标签的对话
All you need to do is create an
你需要做的只是
instance of NFC NDEF Reader
用你的委托
Session with your data gate,
创造一个 NFCNDEFReaderSession 的对象
then invoke to begin method to
然后调用 begin 这一方法
start tag scanning.
来开始标签扫描
If you wish to create a
如果你希望创建一个
multi-tag reading session, set
读取多个标签的对话
the invalidate at the first read
将 invalidateAfterFirstRead
parameter to False.
设为否（False）
If you need to stop an ongoing
如果你需要在程序中
session programmatically, you
停止一个进行中的对话
can call the invalidate method.
你可以调用 invalidate 这一方法
This will trigger your
这将会激活你的 invalidate
invalidate with error callback,
产生错误回调
letting you know that the
告诉你这个对话
session has ended.
结束了
In summary, it is very simple to
总的来说跟随这些步骤
enable NFC tag reading with Core
用 Core NFC 来实现 NFC 标签读取
NFC by following these steps.
是很简单的
Enable the NFC tag reading
启用 NFC
capability.
标签读取功能
Make sure your Scan Usage
保证扫描使用描述字串
Description String is set in
（Scan UsageDescription String）
your info P-list.
在你的属性列表中
Integrate the Core NFC framework
在你的代码中结合
in your code.
Core NFC 框架
And start reading tags.
然后开始读取标签
For more information about this
关于这个演讲的更多信息
presentation and our sample
以及我们的示例代码
code, please visit this online
请访问这个链接
Also, here are some related
还有这里有一些
sessions you might be interested
大家可能感兴趣的
in.
其他演讲
Privacy and Your Apps will
“隐私和你的 app” 将会讨论
discuss important
重要的
privacy-related topics, and
与隐私相关的话题
Wallet will talk about all the
“Apple Pay and Wallet 的最新发展”
exciting Apple Pay features
将会讨论激动人心的、最新将推出的
coming to iOS and Mac OS.
iOS 与 Mac OS 中的 Apple Pay 功能
Thank you for watching this
感谢观看
presentation on Core NFC
这个关于 Core NFC 框架
Framework.
的演讲